Register of the Spartacist League of the U.S. records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Spartacist League Public Issuances, 1964-2016 (Boxes 6-9, 17, 21, 24)
  - Spartacist West (Bay Area regional publication), 1966-1970 (Box-folder 7: 27)
    Vol. 1, no. 1 (1966), no. 2, no. 3, no. 4 (1966 April 29), no. 5 (May 21), no. 6 (July 9), no. 7 (August 29), no. 8 (September 30), no. 9 (December 9), no. 10 (December 29); Vol. 2, no. 1 (1967 August 30), no. 2 (October 3), no. 3 (November 25); whole no. 14 (1968 March 10), no. 15 (April 27), no. 16 (1969 June 27), no. 17 (August 22), no. 18 (1970 March 27).
  - G.I. Voice, no. 1 (February), no. 2/3 (May), no. 4 (July), special (July 5), no. 5 (November), no. 6 (July), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 17: 6)
    Oriented toward soldiers during Vietnam War era.
  - Fort Polk G.I. Voice, unnumbered, undated (Box-folder 17: 7)
  - Amicus curiae briefs, 1984-1988
    The latter two filed on behalf of the Partisan Defense Committee as well as the Spartacist League.
    - Moon and Kamiyama vs. United States, 1984 (Box-folder 7: 28)
      Re First Amendment rights of voluntary organizations.
    - Edwards et al vs. Aguillard et al., 1986 (Box-folder 7: 29)
      Re teaching of creationism.
    - Fort Wayne Books vs. Indiana and Sappenfield et al. vs. Indiana, 1988 (Box-folder 7: 30)
      Re obscenity laws.
  - Pamphlets, 1965-2015
    Includes pamphlets issued by youth affiliates
    - White, Geoffrey. The Student Revolt at Berkeley, 1965 (Box-folder 8: 1)
    - Black and Red: Class Struggle Road to Negro Freedom, 1967 (Box-folder 8: 2)
    - What? Wallace? The Truth about George C. Wallace, 1968 (Box-folder 8: 3)
      Publication of the Committee for a Labor Party.
    - What Is Revolutionary Leadership?, second edition, 1970 (Box-folder 8: 4)
    - Trotsky, Leon. What Is the Permanent Revolution? Three Concepts of the Russian Revolution, 1970 (Box-folder 8: 5)
    - Youth, Class and Party: Basic Documents of the Revolutionary Communist Youth, 1971 (Box-folder 8: 6)
      Publication of Revolutionary Communist Youth.
    - Class Struggle in Auto, 1973 (Box-folder 8: 7)
    - The Fight to Implement Busing: For Labor/Black Defense to Stop Racist Attacks and to Smash Fascist Threats, 1975 (Box-folder 8: 8)
      Publication of the Spartacus Youth League.
    - The Stalin School of Falsification Revisited: Reply to the Guardian, 1975 (Box-folder 8: 9)
    - China's Alliance with U.S. Imperialism, 1976 (Box-folder 8: 10)
    - Stalinism and Trotskyism in Vietnam, 1976 (Box-folder 8: 11)
    - Why the U.S.S.R. Is Not Capitalist: Trotskyism versus Maoism, 1977 (Box-folder 8: 12)
    - The Great Coal Strike of 1978 (Box-folder 8: 13)
    - Lenin and the Vanguard Party, 1978 (Box-folder 8: 14)
    - Solidarnosc: Polish Company Union for CIA and Bankers, 1981 (Box-folder 8: 15)
    - American Workers Revolution Needs Black Leadership, 1982 (Box-folder 8: 16)
    - El Salvador: Military Victory to Leftist Insurgents!, 1982 (Box-folder 8: 17)
    - KAL 007: U.S. War Provocation, 1983 (Box-folder 8: 18)
    - The Socialist Workers Party: An Obituary, 1984 (Box-folder 21: 7)
    - The World Prospect for Socialism: Resolution on the International Situation, Adopted by the British Socialist Labour League at Its 1961 Annual Conference, and Subsequently Amended, 1987 (Box-folder 8: 19)
    - Lutte Ouvrière and Spark: Workerism and National Narrowness, 1988 (Box-folder 8: 20)
    - "Market Socialism" in Eastern Europe, 1988 (Box-folder 8: 21)
    - Trotskyism: What It Isn't and What It Is!, 1990 (Box-folder 8: 22)
    - How the Soviet Workers State Was Strangled, 1993 (Box-folder 8: 23)
    - The International Bolshevik Tendency: What Is It?, 1995 (Box-folder 8: 24)
      Published by the Spartacist League for the International Communist League.
    - Norden's "Group": Shamefaced Defectors from Trotskyism, 1996 (Box-folder 8: 25)
      Published by the Spartacist League for the International Communist League as its International Bulletin, no. 38.
    - Enlightenment Rationalism and the Origins of Marxism, 1998 (Box-folder 17: 8)
    - Imperialism, the "Global Economy" and Labor Reformism, 1999 (Box-folder 17: 9)
    - For Socialist Revolution in the Bastion of World Imperialism! Programmatic Statement of the Spartacist League/U.S., 2000 (Box-folder 17: 10)
    - Marxism vs. Anarchism, 2001 (Box-folder 17: 11)
    - Capitalist Anarchy and the Immiseration of the Working Class, 2009 (Box-folder 21: 8)
    - In Defense of Science and Marxism, 2013 (Box-folder 24: 10)
    - 1934 Strikes: Class-Struggle Leadership Made a Key Difference Then and Now, 2015 (Box-folder 24: 11)
  - Public chronological file, circa 1964-2000
    Leaflets, flyers, declarations, statements, and press releases. Includes youth affiliate issuances; issues of Campus Spartacist.
    - General, circa 1964-2000 (Box-folder 24: 12)
    - 1964 (Box-folder 8: 26)
    - 1965 (Box-folder 8: 27)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 8: 28)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 8: 29)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 8: 30)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 8: 31)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 9: 1)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 9: 2)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 9: 3)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 9: 4)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 9: 5)
  - Election campaign literature, 1968-1985
    Leaflets and flyers on behalf of Spartacist candidates in municipal and state legislative elections.
    See also: Poster Collection, which includes three Spartacist League election posters.
    - New York City, 1968 (Box-folder 9: 6)
    - New York City, 1978 (Box-folder 9: 7)
    - San Francisco, 1980 (Box-folder 9: 8)
    - Detroit, 1981 (Box-folder 9: 9)
    - San Francisco, 1982 (Box-folder 9: 10)
    - Oakland, 1983 (Box-folder 9: 11)
    - San Francisco, 1984 (Box-folder 9: 12)
    - New York City, 1985 (Box-folder 9: 13)
  - Memorial meeting programs, 1982-2015
    - 1982-2002 (Box-folder 17: 12)
    - 2004-2015 (Box-folder 21: 9)
- Partisan Defense Committee Issuances, 1986-2015 (Boxes 9, 17, 21, 24)
  Serial issues, pamphlets, and miscellany, issued by the Partisan Defense Committee, an affiliate of the Spartacist League.
  - Class-Struggle Defense Notes, 1986-2015
    - No. 1 (June), no. 2 (November), no. 3 (December), 1986 (Box-folder 9: 14)
    - No. 4 (March), no. 5 (July), no. 6 (November), 1987 (Box-folder 9: 15)
    - No. 7 (March), special supplement (April), no. 8 (September), no. 9 (November), 1988 (Box-folder 9: 16)
    - No. 10 (April), no. 11 (August), no. 12 (November), 1989 (Box-folder 9: 17)
    - No. 13 (April), no. 14 (November), 1990 (Box-folder 9: 18)
    - No. 15 (Spring/Summer), no. 16 (Fall/Winter), 1991-1992 (Box-folder 9: 19)
    - No. 17 (Spring/Summer), no. 18 (Fall/Winter), 1992-1993 (Box-folder 9: 20)
    - No. 19 (Spring/Summer), no. 20 (Fall/Winter), 1993-1994 (Box-folder 9: 21)
    - No. 21 (Summer/Fall), 1994 (Box-folder 9: 22)
    - No. 22 (Summer), no. 23 (Winter), 1995-1996 (Box-folder 9: 23)
    - No. 24 (Winter), 1996-1997 (Box-folder 9: 24)
    - No. 25 (Winter), 1997-1998 (Box-folder 17: 13)
    - No. 26 (Winter), 1998-1999 (Box-folder 17: 14)
    - No. 27 (Winter), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 17: 15)
    - No. 28 (Winter), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 17: 16)
    - No. 29 (Spring), 2002 (Box-folder 17: 17)
    - No. 30 (Spring), 2003 (Box-folder 17: 18)
    - No. 31 (Summer), 2003 (Box-folder 17: 19)
    - No. 32 (Spring), 2004 (Box-folder 17: 20)
    - No. 33 (Spring), 2005 (Box-folder 21: 10)
    - No. 34 (Spring), 2006 (Box-folder 21: 11)
    - No. 35 (Spring), 2008 (Box-folder 21: 12)
    - No. 36 (Fall), 2010 (Box-folder 21: 13)
    - No. 37 (Spring), 2012 (Box-folder 21: 14)
    - No. 38 (Winter), 2013-2014 (Box-folder 24: 13)
    - No. 39 (Fall), 2015 (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Miscellany, 1989-2001 (Box-folder 9: 25)
    Leaflet, financial report, and pamphlets ( Legal Dossier: The Case of Mumia Abu-Jamal: A Handbook of Constitutional Violations (1990), The Frame-up of Mumia Abu-Jamal (1995) and Mumia Abu-Jamal Is an Innocent Man! (2001)).
  - Amicus curiae brief, Padilla vs. Rumsfeld, 2003 (Box-folder 21: 15)
  - Pamphlets, The Fight to Free Mumia Abu-Jamal and Mumia Is Innocent! Free Him Now!, 2006, 2008 (Box-folder 21: 16)
  - Press releases, 2006-2012 (Box-folder 21: 17)
  - Statements, 2006-2011 (Box-folder 21: 18)
  - Protest letters, 2007-2013 (Box-folder 21: 19)
- Prometheus Research Library Issuances, 1988-2009 (Boxes 10, 17, 21)
  Public bulletins issued by the Prometheus Research Library, an affiliate of the Spartacist League.
  - Prometheus Research Series bulletins, 1988-2007
    - No. 1, Guidelines on the Organizational Structure of Communist Parties, on the Methods and Content of Their Work: Resolution of the Third Congress of the Communist International, 12 July 1921, 1988 (Box-folder 10: 1)
      Includes brochure.
    - No. 2, Documents on the "Proletarian Military Policy,", 1989 (Box-folder 10: 2)
    - No. 3, In Memoriam Richard S. Fraser: An Appreciation and Selection of His Work, 1990 (Box-folder 10: 3)
    - No. 4, Norden, Jan. Yugoslavia, East Europe and the Fourth International: The Evolution of Pabloist Liquidationism, 1993 (Box-folder 10: 4)
    - No. 5, Shachtman, Max. Marxist Politics or Unprincipled Combinationism? Internal Problems of the Workers Party, 2000 (Box-folder 17: 21)
    - No. 6, Selected Speeches and Writings in Honor of Three Women Leaders of the International Communist League (Fourth Internationalist): Martha Phillips, Susan Adams, Elizabeth King Robertson, 2007 (Box-folder 21: 20)
  - Brochure, 2009 (Box-folder 21: 21)
- Youth Affiliate Issuances, 1969-1986 (Boxes 10-12)
  Minutes, internal and public bulletins, newsletters, and position papers issued by successive youth affiliates of the Spartacist League: the Revolutionary Marxist Caucus, Revolutionary Communist Youth, and the Spartacus Youth League.
  - Internal issuances, 1971-1986
    - Minutes, 1971-1985
      Includes attachments.
      - Spartacist League Youth Bureau, 1971 April 19, June 2, 16 (Box-folder 10: 5)
      - Revolutionary Communist Youth National Bureau
        - 1971 October 22, November 7, December 21 (Box-folder 10: 6)
        - 1972 January 9, 23, February 19, March 5, 10, 26, April 23, May 13, 28, June 3, July 20, 26, August 23, 31, September 14, October 4, 30, November 1, 15 (Box-folder 10: 7)
        - 1973 January 16, February 6, March 2, April 6, May 11, July 3, 10, August 7, 16, September 5, October 9, November 2, December 7 (Box-folder 10: 8)
        - 1974 January 8, March 8, May 3, August 3 (Box-folder 10: 9)
      - Revolutionary Communist Youth National Committee
        - 1972 March 31, November 21, 23 (Box-folder 10: 10)
        - 1973 August 17 (Box-folder 10: 11)
      - Revolutionary Communist Youth National Conference, 3rd, 1974 August 25-26 (Box-folder 10: 12)
      - Spartacus Youth League National Bureau
        - 1974 September 30, October 27, December 7, 21 (Box-folder 10: 13)
        - 1975 January 22, March 3, May 6, June 11, 30, July 24, August 6, September 16, December 2 (Box-folder 10: 14)
        - 1976 January 27, March 2, April 6, May 5, June 1, September 12, October 9, December 4 (Box-folder 10: 15)
        - 1977 February 8, March 1, April 4, May 8, June 13, July 18, August 26, November 13 (Box-folder 10: 16)
        - 1978 January 7, April 29, August 26, October 14, December 6 (Box-folder 10: 17)
        - 1979 January 7, July 29, October 28 (Box-folder 10: 18)
        - 1980 January 5, March 24, April 15, May 1, July 14, August 14, September 20, December 3 (Box-folder 10: 19)
        - 1981 July 12, November 8 (Box-folder 10: 20)
        - 1982 August 24, November 2 (Box-folder 10: 21)
        - 1983 February 3, 14, March 26, July 17, October 16 (Box-folder 10: 22)
        - 1984 March 17, October 16 (Box-folder 10: 23)
        - 1985 June 5 (Box-folder 10: 24)
      - Spartacus Youth League National Committee
        - 1974 August 27 (Box-folder 10: 25)
        - 1981 November 28 (Box-folder 10: 26)
        - 1984 November 24 (Box-folder 10: 27)
        - 1985 July 27 (Box-folder 10: 28)
    - Internal bulletins, 1971-1986
      - Revolutionary Marxist Caucus. Pre-Conference Discussion Bulletin
        - No. 1, 1971 August (Box-folder 10: 29)
        - No. 2, 1971 August 27 (Box-folder 10: 30)
        - No. 3, 1971 September 1 (Box-folder 10: 31)
      - Revolutionary Communist Youth
        Title varies: Pre-Conference Discussion Bulletin, Internal Discussion Bulletin.
        - No. 4 [RCY no. 1], 1972 June 1 (Box-folder 10: 32)
        - No. 5 [RCY no. 2], 1972 September 18 (Box-folder 10: 33)
        - No. 6, 1972 November 3 (Box-folder 10: 34)
        - No. 7, 1972 November 19 (Box-folder 10: 35)
        - No. 8, 1973 July 13 (Box-folder 10: 36)
        - No. 9, 1973 July 23 (Box-folder 10: 37)
        - No. 10, 1973 August 3 (Box-folder 11: 1)
        - No. 11, 1974 May 24 (Box-folder 11: 2)
        - No. 12, 1974 June 15 (Box-folder 11: 3)
        - No. 13, 1974 July 29 (Box-folder 11: 4)
        - No. 14, 1974 August 9 (Box-folder 11: 5)
        - No. 15, 1974 August 19 (Box-folder 11: 6)
      - Spartacus Youth League. Internal Discussion Bulletin
        - No. 16, 1975 June 12 (Box-folder 11: 7)
        - No. 17, 1975 July 11 (Box-folder 11: 8)
        - No. 18, 1975 July 28 (Box-folder 11: 9)
        - No. 19, 1975 August 2 (Box-folder 11: 10)
        - No. 20, 1975 August (Box-folder 11: 11)
        - No. 21, 1977 May 7 (Box-folder 11: 12)
        - No. 22, 1977 June 5 (Box-folder 11: 13)
        - No. 23, 1979 April (Box-folder 11: 14)
        - No. 24, 1980 April (Box-folder 11: 15)
        - No. 25, 1980 May (Box-folder 11: 16)
        - No. 26, 1980 August (Box-folder 11: 17)
        - No. 27, 1980 August (Box-folder 11: 18)
        - No. 28, 1981 November (Box-folder 11: 19)
        - No. 29, 1983 July (Box-folder 11: 20)
        - No. 30, 1983 August (Box-folder 11: 21)
        - No. 31, 1983 August (Box-folder 11: 22)
      - Liquidation bulletin. Spartacist League Internal Discussion Bulletin, no. 46, 1986 March (Box-folder 11: 23)
  - Public issuances, 1969-1976
    General note
    See also: Spartacist League Public Issuances/Pamphlets.
    - Revolutionary Marxist Caucus Newsletter, no. 1 (February), no. 2 (March), no. 3 (May-June), no. 4 (September), no. 5 (December), no. 6 (March), 1970-1971 (Box-folder 11: 24)
    - Young Communist Bulletin
      Public bulletins issued successively by Revolutionary Communist Youth and the Spartacus Youth League.
      - No. 1, Documents of the Buffalo Marxist Collective, 1973 January 31 (Box-folder 12: 1)
      - No. 2, International Socialists: Left Wing of Social Democracy, 1973 October 12 (Box-folder 12: 2)
      - No. 3, On the United Front, 1976 (Box-folder 12: 3)
    - Position papers, 1969, 1972 (Box-folder 12: 4)
      Public issuances of the Revolutionary Marxist Caucus and Revolutionary Communist Youth. "The Fight for Women's Liberation" (1969), "Racial Oppression and Working-Class Politics" (1969), and "Out of the Classroom and into the Class Struggle!" (1972).
- International Affiliate Issuances, 1966-2008 (Boxes 12-13, 17-22)
  Minutes, internal bulletins, circulated material, pamphlets, and other printed matter issued by the successive international affiliates of the Spartacist League of the U.S.: the international Spartacist tendency, and the International Communist League (Fourth Internationalist). Includes some issuances of the Spartacist League of the U.S. intended for international audiences, and some issuances of sections outside the United States.
  - Internal issuances, 1973-2003
    - Minutes, 1974-2002
      - European Conference of supporters and sympathizers of the Spartacist tendency, 1974 January 26-27 (Box-folder 12: 5)
      - International Spartacist tendency, Interim International Secretariat
        - 1974 July 22, October 1, 16, 28, December 23 (Box-folder 12: 6)
        - 1975 January 8, February 20, March 17, May 1, 21, July 15, 22, August 10, 13, 20, 29, November 9, December 17 (Box-folder 12: 7)
        - 1976 March 3, October 7, November 14 (Box-folder 12: 8)
        - 1977 May 12, August 3, 5, September 15, 21, October 16, November 9 (Box-folder 12: 9)
        - 1978 August 27, September 22, 26, October 15 (Box-folder 12: 10)
        - 1979 February 26, April 18, May 29, July 1, August 7 (Box-folder 12: 11)
      - International Communist League (Fourth Internationalist), International Secretariat
        - 1990 November 28 (Box-folder 17: 29)
        - 1991 December 21 (Box-folder 17: 30)
        - 1992 June 16, September 8, December 6, 17 (Box-folder 17: 31)
        - 1993 January 8, March 3, April 22, June 7, August 4, September 23, October 22, November 10, December 2 (Box-folder 17: 32)
        - 1994 March 25, April 14, 22, May 18, June 16, July 14, September 2, December 10, 18, 30 (Box-folder 17: 33)
        - 1995 January 10, March 4, 8, 28, April 11, May 9, June 29, July 20, August 31, September 13, November 2, December 7 (Box-folder 17: 34)
        - 1996 January 4, February 4, 18, March 22, April 18, 25, May 9, 11, 21, 28, June 5, 8, 17, July 22, September 2, October 17, November 11, December 11, 22 (Box-folder 18: 1)
        - 1997 February 6, March 21, May 6, 25, June 28, July 31, August 26, October 4, November 1, December 11, 19 (Box-folder 18: 2)
        - 1998 January 9 (Box-folder 18: 3)
        - 1998 February 26, March 30, April 25, May 15, June 15, July 15, August 30, October 28, November 22, December 17 (Box-folder 21: 26)
        - 1999 January 24, February 21, March 20, May 7, August 9, September 5, October 6, 8, November 18, December 22 (Box-folder 21: 27)
        - 2000 January 14, February 8, 18, March 21, 27, May 4, June 16, July 29, August 24, September 28, October 20, December 21 (Box-folder 21: 28)
        - 2001 February 3, March 7, April 25, May 24, June 19, July 3, August 21, October 1, 11, December 7 (Box-folder 21: 29)
        - 2002 January 30, March 7, May 6, 30 (Box-folder 21: 30)
      - International Spartacist tendency, International Secretariat
        - 1979 October 1, November 24-25 (Box-folder 12: 12)
        - 1980 January 4, June 12, 25, December 17 (Box-folder 12: 13)
        - 1981 July 3, August 1, 30, October 8 (Box-folder 12: 14)
        - 1982 September 13 (Box-folder 12: 15)
        - 1984 March 19, October 25 (Box-folder 12: 16)
        - 1985 May 6 (Box-folder 12: 17)
        - 1986 January 8, February 9, November 2 (Box-folder 12: 18)
        - 1987 March 23, September 21 (Box-folder 12: 19)
        - 1988 March 4, November 22 (Box-folder 17: 22)
        - 1989 April 7, September 19, October 31 (Box-folder 17: 23)
      - International Spartacist tendency, International Executive Committee
        - 1977 July 31, August 5 (Box-folder 12: 20)
        - 1978 March 13 (Box-folder 12: 21)
        - 1979 August 25, 29, 31 (Box-folder 12: 22)
        - 1980 August 20, October 19 (Box-folder 12: 23)
        - 1981 September 14, November 28 (Box-folder 12: 24)
        - 1982 March 6-7, April 19, August 22, September 25, 27 (Box-folder 12: 25)
        - 1983 August 17 (Box-folder 12: 26)
        - 1984 August 29-30 (Box-folder 12: 27)
        - 1985 November 30-December 1 (Box-folder 12: 28)
      - International Communist League (Fourth Internationalist), International Executive Committee
        - 1989 November 11 (Box-folder 17: 24)
        - 1990 July 1 (Box-folder 17: 25)
        - 1992 October 30, November 4 (Box-folder 17: 26)
        - 1994 June 28 (Box-folder 17: 27)
        - 1996 January 19-21 (Box-folder 17: 28)
        - 1998 January 29, February 3 (Box-folder 21: 22)
        - 1999 June 27 (Box-folder 21: 23)
        - 2000 July 12 (Box-folder 21: 24)
        - 2001 March 16-18 (Box-folder 21: 25)
      - International Communist League (Fourth Internationalist), Conferences
        - 2nd, 1992 October 31-November 3 (Box-folder 18: 4)
        - 3rd, 1998 January 30-February 2 (Box-folder 21: 31)
      - Internal chronological file
        Circular letters, memoranda, reports, speeches, declarations, proposals, and position papers.
        - 1973 (Box-folder 12: 29)
        - 1974 (Box-folder 12: 30)
        - 1976 (Box-folder 12: 31)
        - 1977 (Box-folder 12: 32)
        - 1980 (Box-folder 12: 33)
        - 1982 (Box-folder 12: 34)
        - 1992 (Box-folder 18: 5)
        - 1993 (Box-folder 18: 6)
        - 1994 (Box-folder 18: 7)
        - 1995 (Box-folder 18: 8)
        - 1996 (Box-folder 18: 9)
        - 1997 (Box-folder 18: 10)
        - 1998 (Box-folder 18: 11, 21: 32)
        - 1999 (Box-folder 21: 33)
        - 2000 (Box-folder 21: 34)
        - 2001 (Box-folder 21: 35)
        - 2002 (Box-folder 21: 36)
    - Internal bulletins, 1973-2003
      Title varies: International Discussion Bulletin, International Information Bulletin, International Internal Bulletin, International Bulletin.
      - Spartacist League of the U.S.
        - Special edition [unnumbered], 1973 February (Box-folder 12: 35)
        - No. 1 [originally Spartacist League Internal Discussion Bulletin, no. 21], 1973 August (Box-folder 12: 36)
        - No. 2, 1974 March (Box-folder 12: 37)
        - No. 3, 1974 May (Box-folder 12: 38)
      - International Spartacist tendency, Interim International Secretariat
        - No. 4, 1975 April (Box-folder 12: 39)
        - No. 5, 1976 May (Box-folder 12: 40)
        - No. 6, 1977 January (Box-folder 12: 41)
        - No. 7, 1977 March (Box-folder 13: 1)
        - No. 8, 1977 May (Box-folder 13: 2)
        - No. 9, 1978 June (Box-folder 13: 3)
        - No. 10, Part I, 1979 January (Box-folder 13: 4)
        - No. 10, Part II, 1979 January (Box-folder 13: 5)
        - No. 11, 1979 June (Box-folder 13: 6)
      - International Spartacist tendency, International Secretariat
        - No. 12, 1979 November (Box-folder 13: 7)
        - No. 13, 1979 December (Box-folder 13: 8)
        - No. 14, 1980 April (Box-folder 13: 9)
        - No. 15, 1980 May (Box-folder 13: 10)
        - No. 16, 1983 November (Box-folder 13: 11)
        - No. 17, 1985 November (Box-folder 13: 12)
        - No. 18, 1987 August (Box-folder 13: 13)
        - No. 19, 1989 March (Box-folder 18: 12)
      - International Communist League (Fourth Internationalist), International Secretariat
        - No. 20, 1991 February (Box-folder 18: 13)
        - No. 21, 1991 June (Box-folder 18: 14)
        - No. 22, 1991 September (Box-folder 18: 15)
        - No. 23, 1991 October (Box-folder 19: 1)
        - No. 24, 1992 January (Box-folder 19: 2)
        - No. 25, 1992 January (Box-folder 19: 3)
        - No. 26, 1992 May (Box-folder 19: 4)
        - No. 27, 1992 September (Box-folder 19: 5)
        - No. 28, 1992 September (Box-folder 19: 6)
        - No. 29, 1992 October (Box-folder 19: 7)
        - No. 30, 1992 October (Box-folder 19: 8)
        - No. 31, 1992 October (Box-folder 19: 9)
        - No. 32, 1994 May (Box-folder 19: 10)
        - No. 33, 1994 May (Box-folder 19: 11)
        - No. 34, 1994 June (Box-folder 19: 12)
        - No. 35, 1994 June (Box-folder 19: 13)
        - No. 36, 1994 June (Box-folder 19: 14)
        - No. 37, 1995 July (Box-folder 20: 1)
        - No. 38, 1996 November (Box-folder 20: 2)
        - No. 39, 1996 December (Box-folder 20: 3)
        - No. 40, 1997 March (Box-folder 20: 4)
        - No. 41, 1997 April (Box-folder 20: 5)
        - No. 42, 1997 August (Box-folder 20: 6)
        - No. 43, 1997 October (Box-folder 20: 7)
        - No. 44, 1997 November (Box-folder 20: 8)
        - No. 45, 1998 January (Box-folder 20: 9)
        - No. 46, 1998 January (Box-folder 20: 10)
        - No. 47, 1998 January (Box-folder 20: 11)
        - No. 48, 1998 March (Box-folder 20: 12)
        - No. 49, 1998 May (Box-folder 20: 13)
        - No. 50, 1998 November (Box-folder 22: 1)
        - No. 51, 1999 March (Box-folder 22: 2)
        - No. 52, 2000 Janurary (Box-folder 22: 3)